# AMRUTA MORE

Borivali West (Mumbai)

9594214365

amrutamahadik1803@gmail.com

Experienced Professional with 4 years responsible for all accounts receivable related functions in a high volume retail environment. Proven competence in efficiently tracking payments. Strong problem-solving and communication skills demonstrated in successful resolution of customer billing issues. Recognized as a dedicated worker who is driven to meet accounts receivable targets and contribute to the company's profitability.

## **SKILLS**

- Organized, detail oriented and has experience in all aspects of A/R.
- Experience in other areas of accounting, Admin etc.
- Comprehensive problem solving skills, excellent verbal and written communication skills,
- ✓ Ability to deal with people diplomatically, willingness to learn, creativity, patience, self confidence and interpersonal relationship building.
- ✓ proven ability to maintain precise records

## **WORK HISTORY**

## CHOICE GROUP OF HOTELS

Accounts Receivables Assistant

June 2019-Currently Working

- Created and maintained the accounting records for the company using IDS Software.
- In charged of the proper invoicing within standard polices reflective of the customer's requirements.
- Worked with any and all personnel to assure timely and accurate invoicing and rating occurs.
- \* Required to interface with departmental managers and occasionally with the Executive Board.
- Handling Accounts Receivables, Credit Control and Debtors Analysis,
- Preparation of Outstanding reports of debtors and taking follow-up of the Outstanding.
- Preparation of MIS reports & proper recognition of revenue and expenses for departmental cost center activity.

Drafting and reviewing all contracts with vendors and other clients

## LYNX COMPUTERS

Nov 2018-April 2019

**Accounts Assistant** 

- Prepared Journal entries, complete general ledger Operations, monthly, year-end closings and draw up and -financial reports and prepare bills of Company.
- Reconciliation of bank accounts, General Ledgers of Debtors,
- Preparing Commission Statements of Vendors.
- Support the company in optimizing our financial transactions and systems by performing reconciliation of payments and customer accounts.
- Perform daily cash management duties, including the recording of bank deposits, updating and distribution of cash receipt logs, and posting of cash to the accounts receivable subledger
- Preparation for GST & Income Tax, TDS etc.
- Exercise integrity and confidentiality in financial reporting, and comply with federal, state, and local financial requirements

## **INTERNSHIPS**

- 1) Internship in Public Concern for Governance Trust (NGO) for One Month (Sept. 2017).
- 2) Internship in State Information Commission with Mr. Ajit Kumar Jain (C.I.C.) for a Week (OCT 2017).

## **EDUCATIONAL BACKGROUND**

A.I.B.E. Exam. Passed in 2020

LLB, Ambedkar College of Law with 69% (Corporate & Banking law) 2015- 2018

MCOM, University of Mumbai with 71%. 2016- 2018

BCOM, Thakur College of Sci & Com with 70%. 2012- 2014

**CERTIFICATES** - Certificate course in TALLY ERP.9 -grade A

-Diploma in Cyber Law (Government law college).

## PERSONAL INFORMATION

DOB : 18<sup>th</sup> March 1993

